

Aleksandar Simeunovic

Experience

Offshore Italy, Rope Access NDT- MPI inspection teamlead on jack up legs. July 12th - August 14th 2024, Shelf Drilling

Offshore Italy, Rope Access NDT- MPI inspection on cranes

June 5th - June 26th 2024, Shelf Drilling

Offshore Electrician at SEMCO, Denmark November 2023 - March 2024

Rope Access DROPS inspection at Shelf Drilling, Italy

July 2023 — Present DROPS Inspection provided for Shelf Dilling Jack- Up Rigs located offshore in Italy

Rope Access at Jack-Up legs, of P1 and P3 Rigs, Replacement of Anodes at LMI company, INGELSIDE OIL AND GAS, Texas, United States April 2023 — May 2023

Rope Access at Jack-Up legs, of P1 and P3 Rigs, Replacement of Anodes INGELSIDE TEXAS, USA Kiewit yard, onshore

Rope Access Technician at LMI company, NOBLE OIL AND GAS, Gulf of Mexico April 2023 — April 2023 Rope access at Derrick Change of Lifting gear slings. NOBLE - STANLEY LAFOSSE Drill ship offshore Gulf of Mexico

Commercial Ventilation Engineer at SITIE GULF QATAR, Doha, Qatar

January 2018 - January 2020

Main task was the installation of the ventilation system. That included multiple team coordination on a daily basis, constant safety adherence for my team, communication between all of the involved work groups in our sector, and with the project manager.

About me

A strong electrical background, and a lifetime of daily use of tools in my family company, have provided me a good base for the completion of most professional tasks that I encounter.

Combined with my rope access experience, inspection diligence and good work ethic, I also bring safe and efficient operations.

My precise solutions,
hazard identification, and adherence to standards have contributed to all the projects I have been a part of.

Contact

L +385989626333

asimeunovic36@gmail.com

Portarol 16, Vodnjan 52215, Croatia

Skills

- -Electrician
- -Rope access
- -NDT inspections
- -Drops inspection
- -Lifting gear inspection
- -Rigging
- -Construction work
- -Painting
- -Oil and gas Industry

Electrician at ULJANIK Group , Pula, Istria, Croatia July 2011 — February 2017

Daily operations for the position were primarily in power distribution, lighting, communication systems, and machinery maintenance.

Education

Electrician, Industrijsko-obrtnička škola Pula, Pula, Croatia

September 2003 - May 2006

(Electrician high-school in Pula)

Certification and courses

IRATA Lv. 1

NDT-MT Lv.2, PT.

EPOXY, AMU - Vests

Confined Space Entry

DROPS inspection

Lifting gear Inspection

BOSIET with (CA-EBS)

HUET

MIST

H2S

L-AUS - Safety When Working on or near Electrical Installations

Atex

Theorical part of § 17 course - Working environment and safety for welding and thermal cutting

Language

Croatian, English

Driver's License

A, B Parachute License

Additional Information

Organizational, computer skills and competencies Hobby: Construction tasks and gym. US B1/B2 Visa